dcurbanmom.com 2019-11-24

# DC Urban Moms and Dads Privacy Policy — DC Urban Moms and Dads

DC Urban Moms and Dads (“we” or “us”) values its visitors’ privacy. This privacy policy is effective January 19, 2013; it summarizes what information we might collect from a registered user or other visitor (“you”), and what we will and will not do with it. 

Please note that this privacy policy does not govern the collection and use of information by companies that DC Urban Moms and Dads does not control, nor by individuals not employed or managed by DC Urban Moms and Dads. If you visit a Web site that we mention or link to, be sure to review its privacy policy before providing the site with information.

**What we do with your personally identifiable information**

It is always up to you whether to disclose personally identifiable information to us. “Personally identifiable information” means information that can be used to identify you as an individual, such as, for example:

  * your name and email address;
  * your DC Urban Moms and Dads user ID and password;
  * any account-preference information you provide us.

If you do provide personally identifiable information to us we will:

  * not sell or rent it to a third party without your permission
  * take commercially reasonable precautions to protect the information from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction;
  * not use or disclose the information except:
    * as necessary to provide services;
    * in other ways described in this privacy policy or to which you have otherwise consented;
    * in the aggregate with other information in such a way so that your identity cannot reasonably be determined (for example, statistical compilations);
    * as required by law;
    * to outside auditors who have agreed to keep the information confidential;
    * as necessary to enforce the Terms of Service;
    * as necessary to protect the rights, safety, or property of DC Urban Moms and Dads, its users, or others; this may include (for example) exchanging information with other organizations for fraud protection and/or risk reduction.

**Other information we collect**

We may collect other information that cannot be readily used to identify you, such as (for example) the domain name and IP address of your computer. We may use this information, individually or in the aggregate:

  * for technical administration of our Web site(s);
  * research and development;
  * customer and account administration;
  * to help us focus our marketing efforts more precisely;
  * in cases of abuse and/or misuse of the website.

**3rd Party Advertisers**

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit [http://www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).

Publisher Common ID: [Opt-Out](https://www.dcurbanmom.com/pub-id.html)

**Cookies**

DC Urban Moms and Dads uses “cookies” to store personal data on your computer. We may also link information stored on your computer in cookies with personal data about specific individuals stored on our servers. If you set up your Web browser (for example, Internet Explorer or Firefox) so that cookies are not allowed, you might not be able to use some or all of the features of our Web site(s). DC Urban Moms and Dads utilizes third party advertisement and analytics services which also utilize cookies over which DC Urban Moms and Dads has no control and to which DC Urban Moms and Dads has no access.

**Your privacy responsibilities**

To help protect your privacy, be sure:

  * not to share your user ID or password with anyone else;
  * to log off the DC Urban Moms and Dads Web site when you are finished;
  * to take customary precautions to guard against “malware” (viruses, Trojan horses, bots, etc.), for example by installing and updating suitable anti-virus software.

**Notice to European Union users**

DC Urban Moms and Dads‘ operations are located in the United States. If you provide information to us, the information will be transferred out of the European Union (EU) to the United States. By providing personal information to us, you are consenting to its storage and use as described herein.

**Information collected from children**

DC Urban Moms and Dads is sensitive to the issue of children's privacy. Hence, our services are neither developed for, nor directed at children under 13 and DC Urban Moms and Dads does not knowingly collect information from children under 13.

**Changes to this privacy policy**

We reserve the right to change this privacy policy as we deem necessary or appropriate because of legal compliance requirements or changes in our business practices. We will post any privacy policy changes on this page.

**Questions or comments?**

If you have questions or comments about DC Urban Moms and Dads‘ privacy policy, contact us via [this link](https://www.dcurbanmom.com/contact-info "Contact Us").
